[
    {
        "question": "What is the concern regarding the shrinking space on aeroplanes?",
        "answer": "The shrinking space on aeroplanes is not only uncomfortable, but it's putting our health and safety in danger."
    },
    {
        "question": "What happened when Rahul Kumar jumped into the lions' enclosure at the zoo?",
        "answer": "Rahul Kumar had to be rescued by security after jumping into the lions' enclosure at the Kamla Nehru Zoological Park in Ahmedabad, and began running towards the animals, shouting he would 'kill them'. Fortunately, he fell into a moat as he ran towards the lions and could be rescued by zoo security staff before reaching the animals."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is on the verge of agreeing a new two-year deal to remain at Nottingham Forest?",
        "answer": "Dougie Freedman"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which clubs are interested in signing Fiorentina goalkeeper Neto?",
        "answer": "Liverpool, PSG, and clubs in Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happened to Pigwig the pig?",
        "answer": "Pigwig fell into a garden swimming pool and was unable to get out, but was eventually rescued by a team of firefighters using slide boards and strops."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the reason for the decline in the amount of time people spend listening to BBC radio?",
        "answer": "The downward trend is blamed on people leading faster-paced lives than in the past, and a change in habits amongst young people who now turn to online streaming services such as Spotify for their music fix."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the spinoff series of Full House?",
        "answer": "The spinoff series is called 'Fuller House'."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the result of the match between Ken Doherty and Reanne Evans?",
        "answer": "Ken Doherty won the match 10-8, extinguishing Reanne Evans' dream of becoming the first women player to play at Sheffield's Crucible Theatre in the world snooker championship."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the snooker match between Evans and Doherty?",
        "answer": "Doherty won the snooker match against Evans."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Mohammed Ali Malek accused of?",
        "answer": "Mohammed Ali Malek was accused of killing 900 men, women and children in one of the worst maritime disasters since World War Two. He was charged with multiple manslaughter, causing a shipwreck and aiding illegal immigration."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the summit of EU leaders on Thursday?",
        "answer": "To discuss further measures to double the resources available to maritime border patrol mission Triton."
    }
]